<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Robbins&#39; Website on Ashley Stallings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sam Robbins&#39; Website on Ashley Stallings</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 21:20:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire Bandit 1 Walkthrough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/bandit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 21:20:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/bandit-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The first few challenges in Bandit are aimed at familiarizing you with the Linux command line. If you&amp;rsquo;ve used Linux before these levels will be a breeze.&#xA;Task The password for the next level is stored in a file called readme located in the home directory.&#xA;Theory man - This is a Linux command that will give you information about any other command your trying to run. It&amp;rsquo;s short for manual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire Bandit 0 Walkthrough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/bandit-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 21:02:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/bandit-0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you have an interest in cybersecurity, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of Capture the Flag. Capture the Flag, or CTF for short, is a cybersecurity game played by those who want to improve their skills. Participants are challenged to find a &amp;ldquo;flag&amp;rdquo; (usually a simple text string), which are hidden somewhere on the vulenerable server , via exploits. OverTheWire.org is a website that hosts free challenges that teaches beginners the basics of CTF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Without CGO</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/cgoless-sqlite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:57:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/cgoless-sqlite/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever been working within a Go project that uses a SQLite database, and been met with the error Binary was compiled with &#39;CGO_ENABLED=0&#39;, go-sqlite3 requires cgo to work. This is a stub OR cgo: C compiler &amp;quot;gcc&amp;quot; not found: exec: &amp;quot;gcc&amp;quot;: executable file not found? This issue occurs commonly on Windows machines when using the popular mattn/go-sqlite3 package. But what causes it and how do we fix it?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
